ceph.com 2014-11-21

# Privacy Statement Ceph

Last Updated: May 15, 2012

Inktank Storage, Inc. (“ **Inktank** “) is committed to protecting the privacy and confidentiality of all personal data we collect when you use the Inktank.com and Ceph.com websites or any related tools and services (“Services”). This Privacy Statement describes information Inktank collects about users, and how that information may be used.

By using the Services, you are agreeing to be bound by the following terms and conditions.

The Services are not directed to children under the age of 13. Inktank does not knowingly collect, or wish to obtain, personally identifiable information from children. If Inktank becomes aware that a user is under the age of 13 and has provided personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental or guardian consent, it will remove user’s personally identifiable information from its files.

This Privacy Policy is part of and incorporated into the Ceph / Inktank Terms of Service at: http://ceph.com/legal-page/terms-of-service.

## What Information We Collect

Inktank may collect three types of information from users of the Services: “personally identifiable information”; “device information” about the device you are using to access our site; and “aggregate information.” 

Personally identifiable information is any piece of information that can potentially be used to uniquely identify, contact, or locate a user of the Services. For example, the Services may collect your name, email address, user name, and telephone number when you set up an account or contact us.

Device information is information about a user’s device and its attributes (such as information about how your browser is configured, whether your device has enabled cookies, its Flash settings, the device’s identification number and other characteristics about the device); it also may be personally identifiable information in cases where it is associated with the name or other identifier for a Site user. We use device information for purposes such as enhancing the user experience and fraud prevention. 

Aggregate information is non-personally identifiable/anonymous information about users of the Sites (such as frequency of visits to Sites, Site pages most frequently accessed browser type). Aggregate information also may include pages visited along with any navigation and in-page interactions used during each visit. In-page interactions monitored include: clicks and selections, mouse movement, page scrolling, and form fields focused on (specific keystrokes entered into each field are not collected). Aggregate information is used in a collective manner and no single person can be identified by that compiled information.

We also use Google Analytics for aggregation and analysis of session information. If you would like to opt-out of Google Analytics, Google has developed a tool that works with major internet browsers to permit you to opt-out. For more information, please visit: http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.

Inktank also uses cookies on the Services. A “browser” or “HTTP” cookie is a unique text file that may be used for data analysis, and enables a web site to tailor information presented to a user based on a user’s browsing program. Inktank may use browser cookies to personalize a user’s pages, to remember a user when the user registers for products or services, for fraud prevention, or to track visits. If a user does not want Inktank or its partners to deploy browser cookies in the user’s browser upon use of the Services, the user may set the browser to reject cookies or to notify the user when a web site tries to place cookies in the browser program. Rejecting cookies may affect a user’s ability to use some of the products, features, or functions of the Services.

Chat rooms, forums, blogs and/or news groups may be available as part of the Services. Any information transmitted by users in these systems is public.

## How We Use Collected Information

Inktank may use personally identifiable information a user submits to understand a user’s needs and create content that is relevant to the user; to generate statistical studies, to improve services, information, and products; to authenticate and communicate with the user; to update users about services, information, and products; to personalize a Site for the user; to troubleshoot problems; to notify the user of any changes with a Site which may affect the user; or to enforce terms of use on a Site.

Personally identifiable information may be publicly available on a Site when a user voluntarily and publicly discloses personally identifiable information, such as when a user posts to a public forum or mailing list. Users may not be able to change or remove public postings once posted. Visitors of these pages may use such personally identifiable information to send unsolicited messages. Inktank is not responsible for any consequences that may occur from the use of personally identifiable information that a user chooses to submit to public pages.

Users may have the opportunity to submit photographs to the Services for product promotions, contests, and other purposes to be disclosed at the time of request. In these circumstances, the Services are designed to allow the public to view, download, save, and otherwise access the photographs posted. By submitting a photograph, users waive any privacy expectations users have with respect to the security of such photographs.

## Who We Share Information With

Inktank will only share the personally identifiable information a user provides with other entities that are part of the Inktank corporate family and/or outside service providers who may be used to provide technical support or otherwise act on Inktank’s behalf. These third party service providers are prohibited from using users’ information for any other purpose, including their own marketing.

Please be advised that in certain instances, it may be necessary for Inktank to disclose a user’s personally identifiable information without a user’s permission to government officials or otherwise as required by legal obligations. Inktank may disclose such personally identifiable information when responding to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise legal rights or defend against claims, including fraud or infringement investigations.

When users choose to provide Inktank with personally identifiable information, users consent to the transfer and storage of such information by Inktank servers in the United States.

## Questions or Concerns

Users who believe that any personally identifiable information we have collected is incorrect, or is, has been, or might be used inappropriately, they must contact us at legal@inktank.com.

Questions or complaints about this Privacy Statement should be sent to legal@inktank.com or sent via postal mail to Privacy Compliance, Inktank Storage, Inc., 707 Wilshire Blvd Suite 5025, Los Angeles, CA 90017.
